<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on K0d3kameraten</title>
    <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on K0d3kameraten</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nb-no</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 21:19:54 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kodekameraten.no/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mac Setup Script</title>
      <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/macsetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 21:19:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kodekameraten.no/post/macsetup/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how to automate the process of making a new mac feel at home for me. So I&amp;rsquo;ve customized a script that does exactly that!
This is shamelessly inspired by, and most of the stuff is a straight copy from bradp.
 Most likely you don&amp;rsquo;t want my setup, but feel free to take a look and rip off what you like! 游뗶 You can find my repo here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ableton Desktop Backgrounds</title>
      <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/ableton-desktop-backgrounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kodekameraten.no/post/ableton-desktop-backgrounds/</guid>
      <description>Here are some desktop backgrounds that I made. Feel free to use them as you wish. You can download them all as a .zip from here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React</title>
      <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/react/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:33:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kodekameraten.no/post/react/</guid>
      <description>This is a part of the series &amp;ldquo;Henry is getting ready for Olavstoppen&amp;rdquo;. You can find the other posts by following the tag &amp;ldquo;Getting Ready 4 OT&amp;rdquo;.
To learn React I have been following this React course by Wes Bos. And the following is mostly my notes and ramblings trying to digest it.
React is, according to reactjs.org, &amp;ldquo;A JavaScript library for building user interfaces.&amp;rdquo;
 Creating our first Component Writing HTML with JSX Linking up your CSS-file Passing dynamic data with Props Routing with React Router Helper functions Events, Refs and this Binding  Events Ref and Binding  Rule number 1: Don&amp;rsquo;t touch the DOM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting ready for Olavstoppen</title>
      <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/getting_ready_for_ot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kodekameraten.no/post/getting_ready_for_ot/</guid>
      <description>I start in my new job at Olavstoppen the 1st of April. Yesterday I got an email with some more information on what technology I will be using: React, React-Native and Redux.
I have some knowledge with React from one small project in class ( and some tinkering on my own ), but I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I&amp;rsquo;m a pro. Not yet at least.
 My goal is to (1.) be efficient in writing code in React, then (2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olavstoppen 01.04.2019</title>
      <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/olavstoppen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 09:46:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kodekameraten.no/post/olavstoppen/</guid>
      <description>Kodekameraten har f친tt seg jobb i Olavstoppen! Den 1. April (ingen sp칮k) starter jeg i 100% stilling som utvikler i Olavstoppen, Stavanger.
Olavstoppen er et datterselskap til Bouvet og har spisset kompetanse p친 digitale brukeropplevelser.
Sammen med 39 andre ansatte skal jeg jobbe med 친 finne de gode l칮sningene. Jeg gleder meg!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>http://kodekameraten.no/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kodekameraten.no/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hallo verden! Mitt navn er Henry, ogs친 kjent som Kodekameraten i enkelte kretser. Velkommen til min nettside.
Kort om meg Jeg er en nysgjerrig, nyutdannet informatiker med et hjerte for de gode opplevelsene. Teknologi interesserer meg, enten det er bleeding-edge eller om det er gjort p친 den gode gamle m친ten. Jeg brenner for 친맍inne praktiske l칮sninger som er tilpasset et behov og trives godt med 친 jobbe i team og tar ansvar for at arbeidet blir gjort.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>